The Guide to the American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
- Series III. Active Member Files, 1913, 191966.
  - Northampton and Bath Railroad Northhampton, Pennsylvania; Mar. 3, 1921 to Aug. 22, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
  - North Louisiana and Gulf Railroad Hodge, Louisiana; Jan. 21, 1921 to May 11, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Charts, correspondence
  - Northwestern Pacific Railroad Suasalito? California; Aug. 1, 1960 to July, August 1964 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Report, booklets
  - Norwood and St. Lawrence Railroad New York City, New York; May 20, 1919 to Oct. 18, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 9-10)
  - Omaha, Lincoln and Beatrice Railway Lincoln, Nebraska; Apr. 20, 1926 to 5, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, applications, exhibits
  - Oregon and Northwestern Railroad Line runs from Senaca, Oregon to [UNK] Oregon; Dec. 16, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Parish Line Railway Kinder, Louisiana; moved to Dallas, Texas; Nov. 24, 1953 to Aug. 15, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 13-15)
    Audit statements, correspondence
  - Patapsco and Back River Railroad Sparrows Point, Maryland; Aug. 16, 1926 to Feb. 24, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Pearl River Valley Railroad Picayune, Mississippi; Nov. 3, 1920 to Dec. 22, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Pecos Valley Southern Railway Pecos, Texas; Dec. 27, 1946 to June 28, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
  - Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England Railroad Bethlehem, Pennsylvania; Apr. 24, 1919 to Feb. 24, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, photos
  - Pickens Railroad Pickens, South Carolina; May 25, 1920 to Mar. 24, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh, Allegheny and McKees Rocks Railroad McKees Rocks, Pennsylvania; June 19, 1919 to June 1, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 22-25)
    Correspondence, application, reports, brochure
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Pittsburgh? Pennsylvania; Dec. 16, 1958 to Aug. 30, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 26-29)
    Government pact, report, maps, speech, brochure
  - Pittsburgh and Ohio Valley Railway Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; May 18, 1951 to Dec. 4, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 30-32)
  - Port Everglades Railway Fort Lauderdale, Florida; Feb. 13, 1943 to Mar. 1, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 33-36)
    Audit report, notice, news article, correspondence
  - Port Huron and Detroit Railroad Bay City, Michigan; Feb. 20, 1923 to May 2, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Port Townsend Railroad Seattle, Washington; Apr. 21, 1954 to May 5, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Rahway Valley Railroad Kenilworth, New Jersey; Nov. 16, 1918 to July 10, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader Railroad Shreveport, Louisiana; Mar. 7, 1927 to Aug. 9, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, news article, brochure
  - River Terminal Railway Cleveland, Ohio; Jan. 10, 1951 to 9, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, postcard, brochure
  - Rockdale, Sandow and Southern Railroad St. Louis, Missouri; July 26, 1923 to Nov. 24, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, petition, application, ICC orders
  - Roscoe, Snyder and Pacific Railway Roscoe, Texas; June 18, 1956 to May 3, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - St. Johnsbury and LaMoille Country Railroad Morrisville, Vermont; Jan. 6, 1938 to July 22, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 8-11)
    Correspondence, ICC orders, show cause order, memo, blueprint
    Stock questions, property and franchise purchase, railroad ownership statutory service, per diem
  - St. Marys Railroad New York, New York; Jan. 15, 1934 to July 22, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Salt Lake, Garfield and Western Railway Salt Lake City, Utah; Nov. 3, 1920 to Sept. 14, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
  - Sandersville Railroad Sandersville, Georgia; Dec. 3, 1920 to Oct. 1, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 15-17)
    Memorial resolution, applications, correspondence, exhibits
  - Sand Springs Railway Sand Springs, Oklahoma; Aug. 10, 1920 to July 6, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 18-22)
    Correspondence, reports, news articles, brochure
  - San Luis Central Railroad Denver, Colorado; Dec. 17, 1920 to Mar. 4, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Santa Maria Valley Railroad Santa Maria, California; Nov. 12, 1920 to May 11, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
  - Savannah State Docks Railroad Savannah, Georgia; May 28, 1953 to 1, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 4-7)
    Prospectus, booklets, financial statements, correspondence
  - Sierra Railroad Jamestown, California; Nov. 3, 1920 to Oct. 7, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Skaneateles Short Line Railroad Skaneateles, New York; June 12, 1919 to July 28, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Map, correspondence, tarrifs, reports
  - South Buffalo Railway Erie County, New York; Sept. 6, 1949 to Sept. 20, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Report, drawings
  - South Georgia Railway Perry, Florida; Dec. 3, 1913 to July 14, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
    ICC application, correspondence, application
    Correspondents: J. W. Oglesby, Pres. South Georgia Railway Bird M. Robinson, Pres. SLRRA
  - Southern Industrial Railroad Centerrille, Iowa; Dec. 7, 1918 to Apr. 28, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 13-16)
    Reports, application, correspondence
  - Southern New York Railway New York, New York; Oct. 30, 1920 to Jan. 2, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Southern Pacific Co. Sausalito? California; Mar. 25, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Southern San Luis Valley Railroad Denver, Colorado; Nov. 26, 1920 to Jan. 7, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 19-20)
  - Springfield Terminal Railway Spring field, Vermont; Dec. 12, 1920 to Apr. 4, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 21-22)
  - State of California operating State Belt Railroad SanFrancisco (?), California; July 25, 1946 to June 27, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Stewartstown Railroad Co. Stewarts town, Pennsylvania; Feb. 11, 1921 to Dec. 20, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Stockton Terminal and Eastern Railroad Stockton, California; Oct. 1, 1954 to Aug. 3, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 25-26)
  - Sumter and Choctaw Railway Bellamy, Alabama; Dec. 17, 1920 to Oct. 21, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 27-29)
  - Tacoma Municipal Belt Line Railway Tacoma, Washington; April 1956 to Dec. 1959, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 30-33)
    Correspondence, memos, map, booklets, financial report, legal brief
  - Tennessee, Alabama and Georgia Railway Chattonooga, Tennessee; June 20, 1919 to Apr. 17, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
    Reports, correspondence, bills
  - Tennessee Railroad Oneida, Tennessee; Jan. 21, 1921 to Dec. 15, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
  - Terminal Railway Alabama State Docks Mobile, Alabama; Jan. 15, 1964 to Apr. 26, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
    News article, correspondence, reports
  - Texas and Northern Railway LoneStar, Texas; Sept. 10, 1948 to Jan. 2, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
  - Texas, Oklahoma and Eastern Railroad DeQueen, Arkansas; Jan. 21, 1932 to Sept. 20, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
  - Texas South-Eastern Railroad Diboll, Texas; Dec. 17, 1920 to Oct. 29, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
    Reports, correspondence, exhibits
  - Tooele Valley Railway Salt Lake City, Utah; July 10, 1919 to July 11, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Trona Railway Trona, Calif; Dec. 22, 1920 to 10, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Pam., correspondence
  - Tucson, Cornelia and Gila Bend Railroad offics in NY, NY; Line runs from Gila, Arizona to Ajo, Arizona; Dec. 17, 1931 to Apr. 23, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
  - Tulsa-Sapulpa Union Railway Sapulpa, Oklahoma; Oct. 18, 1944 to Mar. 27, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    Brochure, correspondence
  - Twin Branch Railroad Fort Branch, Indiana; Mar. 13, 1959 to Dec. 22, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Union Freight Railroad Co. (Boston) Boston, Mass; Sept. 27, 1946 to Jan. 15, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Union Railroad Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.) Pittsburg, Pa; Nov. 5, 1920 to Jan. 21, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Upper Merion and Plymouth Railroad Conshohockee, Pa; Nov. 10, 1954 to Nov. 12, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Ventura County Railway Co. Denver, Colorado; 1/25/32 - 5/12/45 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Vermont Railway runs from Burlington, Vt. to Ratland, Vt., including Bennington, Vt; Dec. 24, 1963 to Mar. 23, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    Magazine, report
  - Virginia and Carolina Southern Railroad Lumberton, North Carolina; Mar. 1, 1930 to Aug. 14, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Blue Ridge Railway Washington, D.C. [UNK] to Piney River, Virginia; Jan. 3, 1921 to Nov. 11, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 28-30)
  - Virginia Central Railway Fredericksburg, Virginia; Jan. 12, 1927 to Mar. 9, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Ware Shoals Railroad Ware Shoals, South Carolina; Mar. 9, 1943 to Apr. 9, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Warren and Saline River Railroad Warren, Arkansas; Aug. 27, 1952 to Sept. 24, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 33-35)
  - Warrenton Railroad Warrenton, North Carolina; Dec. 17, 1920 to Feb. 14, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Warwick Railway Warwick, Rhode Island; Oct. 5, 1949 to [6-22, 1961] (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Washington and Old Dominion Railroad Arlington, Virginia; Dec. 16, 1920 to Nov. 10, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1-6)
    Correspondence, contract, application, booklet
  - Washington, Idaho and Montana Railway Potlatch, Idaho; Apr. 7, 1920 to Apr. 26, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
  - Wellsville, Addison and Galeton Railroad Galeton, Pennsylvania; Dec. 1, 1955 to Dec. 16, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - West Virginia Northern Railroad Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; May 13, 1920 to June 27, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Winfield Railroad Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; Jan. 18, 1918 to Nov. 9, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 12-14)
  - Winifrede Railroad Winifrede, West Virginia; Mar. 7, 1927 to Sept. 10, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
  - Wrightsville and Tennille Railroad Dublin, Georgia; Mar. 12, 1932 to Mar. 27, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Wyandotte Southern Railroad Wyandotte, Michigan; Dec. 17, 1920 to Apr. 19, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Wyandotte Terminal Railroad Detvoit, Michigan; Oct. 13, 1926 to Jan. 31, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, reports, blueprint
  - Yancey Railroad Burnsville, North Carolina; Apr. 6, 1955 to Apr. 16, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 20-21)
  - Yreka Western Railroad Yreka, California; Oct. 16, 1919 to Aug. 16, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 22-24)
- Non- member and Inactive Member Files, 1913-1964.
  Files of non-members, those who often wrote only one time on a specific question and may have been invited to Association membership and files of members who have resigned from the Association, before c. 1964, usually due to complete abandonment of the line or absorption and/or adoption of the road by a larger system. Files are alphabetically arranged and frequently concern abandonments, Association membership, per diem questions and compensation claims against the United States under the provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920.
  - Akron and Barberton Belt Railroad Barberton, Ohio; Feb. 24, 1939 to May 19, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Alamanor Railroad Chester, California; Jan. 10, 1956 to July 8, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny and South Side Railway Pittsburg, Penna; Feb. 6, 1950 to Dec. 16, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Amador Central Railroad Martell, California; Mar. 28, 1919 to July 8, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Arkansas Railroad Star City, Arkansas; July 3, 1920 to Apr. 10, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Reports, Correspondence
  - Arkansas, Louisiana and Northwestern; Aug. 22, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Arkansas Western Railway owns lines in LeFlore County, Oklahoma & Scott County, Arkansas; Apr. 5, 1950 to Sept. 9, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic and Carolina Railroad Kenansville, North Carolina; June 12, 1917 to Feb. 24, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Chemical Co. Malden, Mass; Feb. 21, 1958 to Feb. 27, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Augusta Railroad Star City, Arkansas; Dec. 26, 1918 to Nov. 21, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
    Correspondence, Reports
  - Barre and Chelsea Railroad Montpelier, Vermont; Aug. 1, 1933 to Dec. 24, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 12-16)
    Reports, financial statements, correspondence
  - Bennettsville and Cheraw Railroad Bennettsville, South Carolina; June 6, 1914 to Sept. 14, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 17-19)
    Correspondence, Reports, Maps, Financial statements
  - Big Creek and Telocaset Railroad Pondosa, Oregon; Jan. 31, 1928 to June 15, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 20-21)
  - Blue Ridge Railway Charlotte, North Carolina; Jan. 15, 1921 to Sept. 20, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, Statistical data
  - Bois D'Arc and Southern Railway Randol, Texas & Dallas, Texas; July 26, 1934 to Dec. 19, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Bowden Railway Bowden, Georgia; Dec. 1, 1913 to Dec. 11, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo, Union-Carolina Railroad Union, South Carolina; Jan. 23, 1917 to Jan. 16, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 25-28)
    Correspondence, Reports, Minutes
  - California and Oregon Coast Railroad Grants Pass, Oregon; Sept. 6, 1916 to Feb. 5, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Camp Le Jeune Railroad owned by US Gov't; runs from [UNK] thru Lejeune, military base to Jacksonville, North Carolina; Oct. 22, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Camp Milling Railroad Walton, New York; Sept. 4, 1957 to Sept. 24, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, S urvey
  - Campbell's Creek Railroad Charleston, West Virginia; Oct. 20, 1919 to May 4, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Cane Belt Railroad?; line abandoned between Calhoun to Bonus, Texas; July 19, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Carling Brewing Company Railroad Cleveland, Ohio; Nov. 9, 1956 to Nov. 30, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Carolina Southern Railway Windsor, North Carolina; Jan. 10, 1914 to June 19, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Cassville and Exeter Railway Cassville, Missouri; May 12, 1949 to Mar. 7, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, News articles
  - Castleman River Railroad Mahanoy City, Pajmoved to West Chester, Pennsylvania; June 20, 1949 to Feb. 5, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Caton and Loudon Railway Catonsville(?) Maryland; June 26, 1946 to 7, 192746 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Reports, Correspondence,
  - Central California Traction Co. Stockton, California; May 28, 1920 to Sept. 2, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Central Indiana Railway Anderson, Indiana; Aug. 2, 1951 to May 25, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Central Michigan Northern Railroad Muskegon (?) Michigan; May 19, 1953 to June 8, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Charleston and Western Carolina Railway Georgia (?) South Carolina (?); Nov. 4, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Chesterfield and Lancaster Railroad Line ran from Seaboard Junction to Pageland, South Carolina; Feb. 7, 1940 to Nov. 30, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Chicago and Calumet River Railroad Chicago, Illinois; July 24, 1933 to Mar. 7, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 12-14)
  - Chicago North Shore and Milwaukee Railway Highwood, Illinois; June 30, 1919 to Apr. 15, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, Reports, Newsletter
  - Chicago, St. Paul, Minnesota and Omaha Railway Chicago, [UNK]; Aug. 26, 1948 to Nov. 25, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Chicago, Springfield and St. Louis Railway Springfield, [UNK]; Mar. 6, 1935 to May 28, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, Reports, Telegrams
  - Chihuahua-Pacific Railway El Paso, Texas; Feb. 15, 1955 to Apr. 28, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    Notices
  - Clinton-Anamosa Line Kankakee, Illinois?; July 2, 1949 to July 9, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Cloverdale and Catawba Railroad Cloverdale, Virginia; Apr. 11, 1950 to Jan. 11, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Colorado and Southeastern Railroad Denver, Colorado; Nov. 21, 1918 to Mar. 30, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 21-22)
    Reports, Correspondence, Telegrams, Transcripts
  - Colorado River Western Railway Alleyton, Texas; Sept. 18, 1952 to Aug. 29, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Columbia and Millstadt Railroad St. Louis, Missouri; Mar. 6, 1945 to July 31, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 24-26)
  - Cotton Plant-Fargo Railway Cotton Plant, Arkansas; July 15, 1952 to July 17, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Cowlitz, Chehalis and Cascade Railway Chehalis, Washington; Nov. 3, 1920 to Mar. 30, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Reports, Correspondence, Notices, News articles, Maps
  - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad Cumberland, Maryland; Feb. 8, 1918 to Feb. 15, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    Reports, Blueprints, Correspondence
  - Danville and Western Railway Danville, Virginia; July 1, 1942 to June 7, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Report, Correspondence
  - Davenport, Rock Island and North Western Railway Davenport, Iowa; June 2, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - DeKalb and Western Railroad DeKalb, Mississippi; Nov. 4, 1918 to Aug. 8, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Report, Correspondence, Telegrams
  - Deltic Farm and Timber Co. El Dorado, Arkansas; Dec. 16, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Denver and Intermountain Railroad Denver, Colorado; Dec. 2, 1919 to Mar. 11, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, Report
  - Detroit, Bay City and Western Railroad line runs from Bay City to Port Huron, Michigan; Apr. 16, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Report, Blueprints
  - Detroit, Caro and Sandusky Railway, Caro, Michigan; June 4, 1924 to Dec. 14, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 36-37)
    Correspondence, Memos, Reprints, Photos, Historical exhibits
  - Detroit Terminal Railroad Detroit, Michigan; May 3, 1950 to May 8, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Dexter and Northern Railroad Watertown, New York; June 21, 1949 to July 5, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Durham and Southern Railway Durham, North Carolina; Feb. 26, 1954 to May 10, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - East Broad Top Railroad and Coal Co. Orbisonia, Pennsylvania also Philadelphia office; Sept. 20, 1920 to July 3, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
  - Edgemoor and Manetta Railway Lando, South Carolina; June 24, 1915 to Feb. 13, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Edwards and Western Railroad Edwards (?) Louisiana; Dec. 3, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Emory River Railroad Knoxville, Tennessee; June 9, 1943 to July 9, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Reports, Correspondence, Lists
  - Erie and Michigan Railway and Navigation Co. Chicago, [UNK]; May 20, 1919 to Feb. 4, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
  - Etna and Montrose Railroad Pittsburg, Penna; Apr. 19-19, 19to Aug. 4, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Evangeline Railway Dallas, Texas; Jan. 27, 1941 to Oct. 27, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, Reports, Blueprint
  - Evansville Suburban and Newburgh Railway Evansville, Indiana; Apr. 3, 1922 to July 15, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Reports, Correspondence, Memos
  - Facility Terminal Railroad Kansas City, Missouri; June 4, 1968 to Nov. 17, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Reports, Correspondence, Blue line drawing
  - Feliciana Eastern Railroad Baton Rouge, Louisiana; Apr. 20, 1940 to Jan. 19, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, Memo, Report
  - Flemingsburg and Northern Railroad Louisville Ky. & Flemingsburg kentucky; Nov. 17, 1919 to Jan. 12, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 17-19)
    Reports, Correspondence, Financial Statements, News articles, Newsletters
  - Fort Smith, Subiaco and Rock Island Railroad Paris, ArKansas; May 15, 1918 to July 5, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, Reports, News articles, Blueprint
  - Fort Worth Stock Yards Fort Worth, Texas; Jan. 5, 1948 to May 7, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Franklin and Carolina Railroad Franklin, Virginia; May 7, 1952 to Mar. 3, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Fredericksburg and Northern Railway Fredicksburg, Texas; Mar. 6, 1920 to Jan. 12, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Galesburg and Great Eastern Railroad Indianapolis, Indiana; Sept. 20, 1920 to July 18, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 24-26)
  - Grasse River Railroad Conifer, New York; Dec. 6, 1918 to June 3, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 27-28)
    Correspondence, Reports, Exhibits, Tariff schedule
  - Great Western Railway Denver, Colorado; Mar. 24, 1919 to Jan. 22, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, Reports, Lists
  - Hamlin and Northwestern Railroad Flat Top, Texas runs from Hamlin to Flat Top, Texas; Nov. 8, 1948 to Nov. 10, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    Newspaper clipping, Correspondence
  - Hartford and Slocomb Railroad Hartford, Alabama; Jan. 15, 1954 to Feb. 25, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, Reports, Tariffs
  - Helena and Northwestern Railway Helena, Arkansas; Dec. 2, 1948 to Apr. 8, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    Reports, Correspondence, Memos, Map, Article
  - Helena Southwestern Railroad West Helena, Arkansas; July 16, 1923 to Sept. 18, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, Reports, News article
  - Hickman Railroad Hickman (?), Kentucky(?); May 7, 1951 to May 10, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Hillsdale and South Western Railroad Michigan; Aug. 13, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Huntindon and Broad Top Mountain Railroad no reference made to location; n.d. (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Illinois Missouri Terminal Railway Co. no reference made to location; Apr. 2, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Indiana Northern Railway moved from South Bend, Indiana to Chiago, [UNK]; Aug. 10, 1920 to Nov. 2, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Notices, Correspondence, Memos, Reports
  - Jacksonville Northwestern Railway Jacksonville, Arkansas; Apr. 9, 1951 to Nov. 11, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Jacksonville Terminal Co. Jacksonville, Florida; Feb. 20, 1958 to Feb. 24, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Joe Cushing Railroad Fitchburg, Massachusetts; May 3, 1948 to May 5, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    Correspondence, News article
  - Joplin-Pittsburg Railroad Pittsburg, Kansas; Jan. 9-19 for 2-26, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    Reports, News articles, Correspondence
  - Kahului Railroad Kahului, Maui, T.H; Sept. 29, 1954 to Oct. 20, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Kansas City Connecting Railroad Kansas City Missouri (?); Jan. 30, 1946 to Mar. 22, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Kansas City, Kaw Valley, and Western Railroad Kansas City, Kansas; Sept. 23, 1918 to Aug. 9, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Reports, Correspondence, News articles, Vouchers
  - Kingsport Railroad Kingsport, Tennessee (?); Jan. 23, 1947 to Mar. 20, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Lake Champlain and Moriah Railroad Port Henry, New York; Nov. 12, 1918 to Dec. 8, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lakeland Railway Valdosta, Georgia and Lakeland, Georgia; May 14, 1921 to Nov. 10, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 9-11)
  - Lawndale Railway and Industrial Co. Lawndale, North Carolina; Apr. 11, 1914 to Jan. 15, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
    Correspondence, Report, Maps
  - Ligonier Valley Railroad Ligonier, Pennsylvania; May 12, 1918 to Dec. 9, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 14-16)
  - Lincoln, Nebraska Municipal Railway Lincoln, Nebraska; n.d. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Memos
  - Litchfield and Madison Railway Chicago, Illinois; Aug. 23, 1920 to Feb. 4, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Lorain and Southern Railroad Cleveland, Ohio; Feb. 25, 1918 to July 18, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
  - Los Angeles Junction Railway Los Angeles County, California; Oct. 28, 1924 to July 30, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Reports, Correspondence, Certificate
  - Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Shreveport, Louisiana; Jan. 16, 1918 to Feb. 26, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Louisville, New Albany and Corydon Railroad Corydon, Indiana; Apr. 30, 1918 to Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 23-24)
  - Manchester and Oneida Railway Manchester, Iowa; Jan. 24, 1918 to Sept. 23, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 25-26)
    Reports, Correspondence, News articles
  - Mansfield Railway and Transportation Co. Monroe, Louisiana; Dec. 13, 1920 to July 23, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 27-28)
    Reports, Memo, Correspondence
  - Manistee and Northeastern Railway Manistee, Michigan; Jan. 30, 1919 to Dec. 2, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 29-32)
  - Marcellus and Otisco Co. Marcellus, New York; Mar. 22, 1918 to May 13, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - Middle Creek Railroad Chicago, [UNK]; Nov. 13, 1920 to Mar. 14, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
  - Middle Fork Railroad [UNK], Ohio; Sept. 20, 1948 to July 12, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Midland Continental Railroad Akron, Ohio; July 29, 1929 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Report, Blueprint
  - Midland Terminal Railway Colorado Springs, Colorado; Aug. 20, 1918 to Aug. 25, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Report, Correspondence, memos